Effective immediately.
ساري المفعول فورًا.
I, Xiao Yaqi, am officially terminating my contract with Qingmu Group.
أنا، شياو يا تشي، أنهي رسميًا عقدي مع مجموعة تشينغمو.
I will no longer be the spokesperson for Qingmu Group.
لن أكون المتحدث الرسمي لمجموعة تشينغمو بعد الآن.
No.
لا.
What? Xiao Yaqi canceled her endorsement?
ماذا؟ شياو ياتشي ألغت تأييدها؟
How could this happen?
كيف يمكن أن يحدث هذا؟
Everyone, don't listen to her nonsense.
الجميع، لا تستمعوا إلى هراءها.
Our Qingmu Group's products
منتجات مجموعة تشينغمو
have no quality issues whatsoever.
لا توجد أي مشاكل في الجودة على الإطلاق.
Su Qingyan, stop wasting your time.
سو تشينغيان، توقفي عن إضاعة وقتك.
They won't believe you.
لن يصدقوك
This is the influence I have as a top celebrity.
هذا هو التأثير الذي أتمتع به كشخصية مشهورة.
Understand?
يفهم؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Miss Xiao is a top celebrity.
السيدة شياو هي من المشاهير المشهورين.
If your products weren't problematic
إذا لم تكن منتجاتك مشكلة
why would she suddenly break the contract and risk her reputation?
لماذا تقوم فجأة بخرق العقد وتخاطر بسمعتها؟
You put faulty products on the market
لقد وضعت منتجات معيبة في السوق
that's being irresponsible to consumers.
وهذا يعتبر عدم مسؤولية تجاه المستهلكين.
Crooked merchants, I spit on you.
أيها التجار الفاسدون، أنا أبصق عليكم.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Crooks, liars.
المحتالون، الكاذبون.
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
Liars, crooks.
كاذبون، محتالون.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
You are journalists,
أنتم صحفيون،
spreading rumors without evidence,
نشر الشائعات دون دليل،
only listening to one side of the story.
الاستماع فقط إلى جانب واحد من القصة.
Do you have any professional ethics?
هل لديك أية أخلاقيات مهنية؟
And you, as a famous celebrity,
وأنت، كشخصية مشهورة،
broke the contract on the spot and made false accusations.
انتهك العقد على الفور ووجه اتهامات كاذبة.
Looks like you don't want to be a star anymore.
يبدو أنك لم تعد ترغب في أن تكون نجمًا بعد الآن.
Threatening me?
تهديدي؟
Oh, I'm so scared.
أوه، أنا خائفة جدًا.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك
this is the price you pay for humiliating me yesterday.
هذا هو الثمن الذي تدفعه لإذلالي بالأمس.
So, how about it?
إذن ماذا عن ذلك؟
Do you like the big gift I gave you?
هل أعجبتك الهدية الكبيرة التي قدمتها لك؟
Xiao Yaqi, you signed a contract with our Qingmu company.
شياو يا تشي، لقد وقعت عقدًا مع شركتنا تشينغمو.
This counts as breaching the contract.
ويعتبر هذا بمثابة خرق للعقد.
Aren't you afraid of being blacklisted by the agency?
ألا تخاف من أن يتم إدراجك في القائمة السوداء من قبل الوكالة؟
I was forced to sign the contract because the agency threatened me.
أُجبرت على توقيع العقد لأن الوكالة هددتني.
But now?
ولكن الآن؟
I have even more powerful backing now.
لقد حصلت على دعم أقوى الآن.
I've even received an invitation from the famous international director Zhang Yimu.
لقد تلقيت أيضًا دعوة من المخرج الدولي الشهير تشانغ ييمو.
I'll soon become an international superstar.
سأصبح قريبًا نجمًا عالميًا.
By then,
بحلول ذلك الوقت،
even the agency will have to listen to me.
حتى الوكالة سوف تضطر إلى الاستماع إلي.
So what if I break the contract?
فماذا لو خالفت العقد؟
What can you do to me?
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل بي؟
Well said.
أحسنت القول.
Young Master Song is here.
السيد الشاب سونغ هنا.
Young Master Song is here—it's him!
السيد الشاب سونغ هنا - إنه هو!
What kind of status does Miss Xiao have?
ما هو نوع المكانة التي تتمتع بها الآنسة شياو؟
How could she possibly lower herself to sign with your Qingmu?
كيف يمكنها أن تخفض نفسها للتوقيع مع تشينجمو الخاص بك؟
Happy to have gotten the Immortal Doctor's secret recipe.
سعيد لأنني حصلت على الوصفة السرية للطبيب الخالد.
Weren't you acting all arrogant and cocky before?
ألم تكن تتصرف بغطرسة وغرور من قبل؟
Why aren't you showing off now?
لماذا لا تتفاخر الآن؟
You two planned this together, didn't you?
لقد خططتم لهذا معًا، أليس كذلك؟
But who gave you the confidence
ولكن من أعطاك الثقة؟
to think you've already won?
هل تعتقد أنك فزت بالفعل؟
Gao Xing, you're still being stubborn now?
جاو شينغ، هل مازلت عنيدًا الآن؟
Miss Xiao has already canceled her partnership with you.
لقد ألغت السيدة شياو شراكتها معك بالفعل.
All the reporters here were invited by me to watch you make a fool of yourselves.
لقد تمت دعوة جميع المراسلين هنا من قبلي لمشاهدتكم وأنتم تجعلون من أنفسكم أضحوكة.
After such a scene,
بعد هذا المشهد،
your product will be completely ruined.
سيتم تدمير منتجك بالكامل.
You won't be able to sell a single item then.
لن تتمكن من بيع عنصر واحد بعد ذلك.
Let's see how you recover from this.
دعونا نرى كيف تتعافى من هذا.
Su Qingyan, I'll give you one last chance.
سو تشينغيان، سأمنحك فرصة أخيرة.
As long as you divorce this Gao right now,
طالما أنك تطلق هذا القاو الآن،
and marry into our Song family,
وتزوج من عائلة سونغ،
I can let Qingmu off the hook.
أستطيع أن أترك تشينجمو بعيدًا عن المشكلة.
But you need to think carefully.
ولكن عليك أن تفكر بعناية.
This promise I'm making
هذا الوعد الذي أقدمه
is only valid right now.
صالحة الآن فقط.
After all, if you miss this opportunity,
بعد كل شيء، إذا ضيعت هذه الفرصة،
you won't get another one.
لن تحصل على واحدة أخرى.
Keep dreaming.
استمر بالحلم.
Fine.
بخير.
Since you're asking for trouble,
بما أنك تطلب المتاعب،
don't blame me for being ruthless.
لا تلوموني على كوني قاسيًا.
Everyone,
الجميع،
Qingmu Group's products are counterfeit.
منتجات مجموعة Qingmu مزيفة.
Their quality is poor.
جودتها رديئة.
Miss Xiao spoke out bravely.
تحدثت الآنسة شياو بشجاعة.
She canceled the contract in public.
ألغت العقد علنا.
This is big news.
هذه أخبار كبيرة.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Hurry up and take pictures.
اسرع والتقط الصور.
Quick, get it all on camera.
سريعًا، قم بتصوير كل شيء أمام الكاميرا.
Take the pictures, hurry!
التقط الصور، بسرعة!
Stop taking pictures.
توقف عن التقاط الصور.
This really is big news.
هذه حقا أخبار كبيرة.
Qingyan, something bad happened.
تشينغيان، حدث شيء سيء.
The news about Xiao Yaqi terminating her contract is trending.
الخبر حول إنهاء شياو ياتشي لعقدها أصبح رائجًا.
What?
ماذا؟
And it's getting even more attention.
ويحظى هذا الأمر بمزيد من الاهتمام.
Hey, look, look!
مهلا، انظر، انظر!
Xiao Yaqi announced she's ending her contract with Qingmu Group.
أعلنت شياو ياتشي أنها أنهت عقدها مع مجموعة تشينغمو.
Is this true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
What does this mean?
ماذا يعني هذا؟
Really?
حقًا؟
Product fraud.
احتيال المنتج.
Qingmu Group has gone too far.
لقد ذهبت مجموعة تشينغمو بعيدًا جدًا.
A shady company like this deserves to go bankrupt.
شركة مشبوهة مثل هذه تستحق الإفلاس.
Wow.
رائع.
Zhixi, sis.
زيكسي، أختي.
You look absolutely stunning today.
أنت تبدو مذهلة تماما اليوم.
The judges will vote live tonight.
سوف يقوم القضاة بالتصويت على الهواء مباشرة الليلة.
You'll definitely beat Liu Bingxin.
سوف تتغلب على ليو بينجكسين بالتأكيد.
Best Actress is definitely yours.
جائزة أفضل ممثلة هي بالتأكيد من نصيبك.
Of course. Whatever I, Ye Zhixi, want,
بالطبع. مهما أردتُ أنا، يي تشي شي،
Liu Bingxin isn't even worthy to compete with me.
ليو بينجكسين لا يستحق حتى التنافس معي.
I heard Xiao Yaqi terminated her contract.
سمعت أن شياو ياتشي أنهت عقدها.
What are they talking about?
ماذا يتحدثون عنه؟
I heard it's a company in Yuncheng.
سمعت أنها شركة في يونتشنغ.
They're holding a press conference for a new spokesperson.
إنهم يعقدون مؤتمرا صحفيا للمتحدث الجديد.
Xiao Yaqi announced the contract termination in public at the event.
أعلن شياو ياتشي عن إنهاء العقد علنًا في هذا الحدث.
It's all over the trending searches.
إنه موجود في جميع عمليات البحث الشائعة.
Let me take a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
It's him.
إنه هو.
Why is he here too?
لماذا هو هنا أيضا؟
Zhixi, you know him?
تشيكسي، هل تعرفه؟
Know him? It's more than that.
هل تعرفه؟ إنه أكثر من ذلك.
I've had such a hard time looking for this heartless man.
لقد كان من الصعب جدًا بالنسبة لي البحث عن هذا الرجل عديم القلب.
Quick, get the car ready.
سريعًا، جهّز السيارة.
Take me to the press conference venue.
خذني إلى مكان المؤتمر الصحفي.
To the press conference venue?
الى مكان المؤتمر الصحفي؟
What about the awards ceremony?
ماذا عن حفل توزيع الجوائز؟
If you leave now,
إذا غادرت الآن،
the Golden Dragon Best Actress award will go to Liu Bingxin.
جائزة التنين الذهبي لأفضل ممثلة ستذهب إلى الممثلة ليو بينجكسين.
If she wants it, let her have it.
إذا أرادت ذلك، فلتحصل عليه.
But this man—I'm definitely taking him.
لكن هذا الرجل - سأختاره بالتأكيد.
Bingxin,
بينجشين،
Good news!
اخبار جيدة!
Ye Zhixi just announced she's dropping out of the ceremony.
أعلنت Ye Zhixi للتو أنها ستنسحب من الحفل.
She left in a car right away.
غادرت بالسيارة على الفور.
The Golden Dragon Best Actress award is definitely yours now.
جائزة التنين الذهبي لأفضل ممثلة أصبحت الآن من نصيبك بالتأكيد.
What? She left?
ماذا؟ هل غادرت؟
Where did she go?
أين ذهبت؟
They say she saw some news report.
يقولون أنها رأت بعض التقارير الإخبارية.
She went next door to attend some press conference.
ذهبت إلى الغرفة المجاورة لحضور مؤتمر صحفي.
Press conference news?
أخبار المؤتمر الصحفي؟
Show me.
أرِنِي.
Qingmu Group's Xiao Yaqi.
مجموعة تشينغمو شياو ياكي.
What does she have to do with Ye Zhixi?
ما علاقتها بـ Ye Zhixi؟
Wait.
انتظر.
It's him.
إنه هو.
He's here too.
وهو هنا أيضا.
Who is that? Do you know him?
من هذا؟ هل تعرفه؟
I know him very well.
أنا أعرفه جيدا.
Well, well, Ye Zhixi.
حسنًا، حسنًا، Ye Zhixi.
No wonder you don't even care about the Best Actress award.
لا عجب أنك لا تهتم حتى بجائزة أفضل ممثلة.
Get the car ready. Take me there right now.
جهّز السيارة. خذني إلى هناك الآن.
Ah!
اه!
But the award ceremony is about to start.
لكن حفل توزيع الجوائز على وشك أن يبدأ.
If you go now,
إذا ذهبت الآن،
won't you miss the Best Actress award for nothing?
هل ستفوتك جائزة أفضل ممثلة بلا سبب؟
Who cares about the Best Actress award?
من يهتم بجائزة أفضل ممثلة؟
Whoever wants it can have it.
من يريده يستطيع الحصول عليه.
If I don't go now, someone will steal my man.
إذا لم أذهب الآن، سوف يسرق شخص ما رجلي.
Get the car ready.
جهز السيارة.
Gao Xing, did you see that?
جاو شينغ، هل رأيت ذلك؟
This is what happens when you go against me, Song Haoyang.
هذا ما يحدث عندما تذهب ضدي، سونغ هاويانغ.
In the face of our Song family's power,
في مواجهة قوة عائلة سونغ،
you, just a delivery guy,
أنت مجرد رجل توصيل
are nothing at all.
لا شيء على الإطلاق.
You call this power?
هل تسمي هذا قوة؟
Then you really have no idea what power means.
إذن ليس لديك أي فكرة عما تعنيه القوة.
Keep pretending.
استمر بالتظاهر.
Go on, keep pretending.
إستمر، إستمر في التظاهر.
Looking at you from head to toe,
أنظر إليك من الرأس إلى أخمص القدمين،
your mouth is the only tough thing about you.
فمك هو الشيء القوي الوحيد فيك.
Su Qingyan, it's not too late to regret now.
سو تشينغيان، ليس من المتأخر جدًا الندم الآن.
As long as you kick this Gao guy away right now,
طالما أنك تطرد هذا الرجل غاو الآن،
and marry me,
وتزوجيني
I can put in a good word for you with Miss Xiao.
أستطيع أن أقول لك كلمة طيبة مع الآنسة شياو.
Of course, I, Xiao Yaqi, will give Young Master Song some respect.
بالطبع، أنا، شياو ياتشي، سأعطي السيد الشاب سونغ بعض الاحترام.
Let Su Qingyan remarry on the spot.
دع سو تشينغيان يتزوج مرة أخرى على الفور.
And have the two of them kneel and apologize to me right here.
واجعل الاثنين يركعون ويعتذروا لي هنا.
If I'm in a good mood,
إذا كنت في مزاج جيد،
I won't pursue today's matter any further.
لن أتابع موضوع اليوم أكثر من ذلك.
No way.
مستحيل.
Even if it costs me all of Qingmu,
حتى لو كلفني ذلك كل تشينجمو،
I still won't agree to any of your demands.
أنا لن أوافق على أي من مطالبك.
Well said, honey.
أحسنت القول يا عزيزتي.
But don't worry.
ولكن لا تقلق.
If they want to mess with Qingmu,
إذا أرادوا العبث مع تشينجمو،
just the two of them,
فقط الاثنين منهم
they don't have what it takes.
ليس لديهم ما يلزم.
Gao Xing, you sure talk big.
جاو شينغ، أنت بالتأكيد تتحدث بشكل كبير.
What else can you do?
ماذا يمكنك أن تفعل أيضاً؟
Show us if you have any skills.
أظهر لنا إذا كان لديك أي مهارات.
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
Didn't you say you know Chu Jiangchao, President Chu?
ألم تقل أنك تعرف تشو جيانغ تشاو، الرئيس تشو؟
Why don't you call him right now and see?
لماذا لا تتصل به الآن وترى؟
Who knows,
من يعلم؟
maybe he'll send you a new spokesperson.
ربما سيرسل لك متحدثًا جديدًا.
And stop calling me President Chu.
وتوقفوا عن مناداتي بالرئيس تشو.
Perfect timing.
توقيت مثالي.
Isn't the Golden Dragon Festival awards ceremony being held right here in our Yun City?
أليس حفل توزيع جوائز مهرجان التنين الذهبي يقام هنا في مدينة يون؟
Ye Zhixi and Liu Bingxin, both international award-winning actresses,
Ye Zhixi وLiu Bingxin، كلاهما ممثلتان حائزتان على جوائز دولية،
aren't far from here either.
ليست بعيدة عن هنا أيضًا.
Gao Xing, with your abilities,
جاو شينغ، مع قدراتك،
making a call to invite both actresses over
إجراء مكالمة لدعوة الممثلتين
shouldn't be too hard, right?
لا ينبغي أن يكون الأمر صعبًا للغاية، أليس كذلك؟
That way, everyone here can bask in their glory too.
بهذه الطريقة، يمكن للجميع هنا أن يستمتعوا بمجدهم أيضًا.
Boss, your two old flames
يا رئيس، حبيباك القديمان
have seen the news.
لقد رأيت الأخبار.
They're on their way to you right now.
إنهم في طريقهم إليك الآن.
They'll be here soon.
سيكونون هنا قريبا.
They're on the way, almost here.
إنهم في الطريق، قريبون جدًا.
What? Who's almost here?
ماذا؟ من يقترب من هنا؟
Did I hear that right?
هل سمعت ذلك بشكل صحيح؟
Young Master Song, did you hear that?
السيد الشاب سونغ، هل سمعت ذلك؟
It sounds like Gao Xing is saying
يبدو أن قاو شينغ يقول
both international actresses are on their way here.
الممثلتان العالميتان في طريقهما إلى هنا.
Hey, Gao,
مهلا، غاو،
there's a limit to how much you can brag.
هناك حد لما يمكنك التباهي به.
Ye and Liu are coming to Yun City
يي وليو قادمان إلى مدينة يون
to attend the Golden Dragon Festival.
لحضور مهرجان التنين الذهبي.
They're waiting for the awards ceremony right now.
إنهم ينتظرون حفل توزيع الجوائز الآن.
They're competing for Best Actress.
إنهم يتنافسون على جائزة أفضل ممثلة.
Who do you think you are?
من تعتقد نفسك؟
You think they'd skip the awards just to come see you?
هل تعتقد أنهم سيتخطون حفل توزيع الجوائز فقط من أجل رؤيتك؟
Do you take us all for fools?
هل تعتبرنا جميعا حمقى؟
Exactly, that's impossible.
بالضبط، هذا مستحيل.
Gao Xing,
جاو شينغ,
let me teach you something.
دعني أعلمك شيئا.
If someone is truly capable,
إذا كان شخص ما قادرًا حقًا،
it's not because of bragging or sweet talk.
ليس بسبب التفاخر أو الكلام المعسول.
No matter how much you say,
بغض النظر عن مقدار ما تقوله،
you're still just a clown.
أنت لا تزال مجرد مهرج.
I told you,
أخبرتك،
don't be in such a hurry.
لا تستعجل.
Soon you'll see who the real clown is.
سوف ترى قريبا من هو المهرج الحقيقي.
Everyone,
الجميع،
Gao Xing just said
قال جاو شينغ للتو
that their Qingmu Group
أن مجموعة تشينغمو الخاصة بهم
will soon have a new spokesperson.
سيكون له متحدث جديد قريبا.
And,
و،
it's an international superstar even more famous than Miss Xiao.
إنه نجم عالمي أكثر شهرة من الآنسة شياو.
Young Master Song is right.
السيد الشاب سونغ على حق.
What are you all waiting for?
ماذا تنتظرون جميعا؟
Turn your cameras to the entrance.
وجه كاميراتك نحو المدخل.
Maybe,
ربما،
the new spokesperson is about to arrive.
المتحدث الجديد على وشك الوصول.
Gao Xing, you brought this on yourself.
جاو شينغ، أنت جلبت هذا على نفسك.
In front of so many media reporters,
أمام العديد من مراسلي وسائل الإعلام،
you made such outrageous claims.
لقد قدمت مثل هذه الادعاءات الشنيعة.
I guarantee
انا اضمن
from today on,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
you'll be the biggest joke in Yun City.
سوف تكون أكبر نكتة في مدينة يون.
International film queen Ye Zhixi.
ملكة السينما العالمية Ye Zhixi.
Miss Ye has arrived.
لقد وصلت السيدة يي.
Now I want to see who dares to laugh at him.
الآن أريد أن أرى من يجرؤ على الضحك عليه.